<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Geeky Blogs</title><link>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Geeky Blogs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 18:19:25 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Artificial Intelligence and Robotics In A Nutshell</title><link>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/post-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 18:19:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/post-1/</guid><description>Artificial Intelligence is an umbrella term and describes the broad approach of using machines to imitate intelligent human behavior in order to solve problems.</description></item><item><title>Drone Software and Development</title><link>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/post-8/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 18:19:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/post-8/</guid><description>Drones allow opening previously unavailable opportunities – to see the invisible and reach the unreachable – not only in the air but also on the ground and underwater.</description></item><item><title>Github Repository Controls</title><link>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/post-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 18:19:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/post-4/</guid><description>Github Tutorial: How to Make Your First GitHub Repository
A critical skill for developers of all experience levels is proficiency in GitHub.</description></item><item><title>My work from home workstation</title><link>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/post-5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 18:19:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/post-5/</guid><description>The Pros and Cons of Working from Home as a Web Developer The US Occupational Outlook Handbook estimates that by 2024, there will be a 27% increase in the job prospects for this kind of expertise, due to the increasing use of mobile devices and e-commerce.</description></item><item><title>Robots Transformimg our Future</title><link>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/post-7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 18:19:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/post-7/</guid><description>“A robot is an autonomous machine capable of sensing its environment, carrying out computations to make decisions, and performing actions in the real world.</description></item><item><title>What is a Virtual Assistant</title><link>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/post-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 18:19:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/post-3/</guid><description>What is a virtual assistant? A virtual assistant is a virtual employee hired as an executive or administrative assistant for your business who works remotely.</description></item><item><title>What you need to know about Programming</title><link>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/post-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 18:19:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/post-2/</guid><description>What is Programming?
We all have heard about Computer Programming gaining a lot of popularity in the past 3 decades. So many students these days want to opt for a Computer Science stream in order to get a job at their dream tech company - Google, Facebook, Microsoft, Apple, and whatnot.</description></item><item><title>Why you need to learn PHP</title><link>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/post-6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 18:19:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>geeky-blogs.netlify.app/blog/post-6/</guid><description>PHP is a popular programming language which is utilized to build dynamic web applications with MySQL database connections. For a programming language to be successful, it must be comfortable and widely accepted by a large number of web developers.</description></item></channel></rss>